check out this raw vegan Korean barbecue
Feast I made from raw Chef yin's brand
new course first up from rawf yin's raw
Korean barbecue I'm going to try some
portello proi yeah I love Portell are so
good yeah I got some secret yums in the
secret Special Sauce going to mix it all
up time to add in the mushrooms and mix
it all up I have a couple white ones cuz
I ran out of port yeah into the
dehydrator you go up next to making
carrot the I'm probably pronouncing that
word and I'm going to grate it instead
of Julie in it because I'm in a bit of a
rush sorry time to make the paste sauce
for this Bo oh yeah time to stir that up
and let it marinate smells really good
beautiful beautiful next up making some
cauliflower rice but that's not the only
thing in there post for me post for me
post for me turn into rice and I must
say this rice is more than nice and
definitely not ice rashen I'm excited to
put this all together oh yeah you're all
done for a little bit of garnish oh yeah
little bit of finely chopped green
onions B bing bada boom black and white
sesame seeds oh yeah oh oh hello hello
and but a pinch black pepper
boom let's dig in oh gosh look at this
seriously look at this raw vegan Korean
barbecue Feast Raj cheffen you're a
magician I'm going to grab a leaf of
Roma and fill it up with that some of
this some of this bada bing bada
oh my
go
seriously
mhm
mhm so dang good and just a few of the
recipes from the
book
mhm and each bite gets better rashan
thank you so much this is ridiculously
delicious unique flavors I have not had
before cuz I don't think I've had this
kind of Korean barbecue and this is just
three of many recipes in her new course
available now in the ultimate raw vegan
bundle not much longer only until 11:59
p.m. PST on the 12th that's Sunday
that's tomorrow so you're going to want
to check it out it is really damn good
and it's just one of 33 books courses
available now but gone forever after
tomorrow night check it out check it out
I'm going to dive in more and it's time
to get into some lives much peace love
and see not fruit